
{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How long does it take sunlight to reach the earth?","correct_answer":"8 min","incorrect_answers":["1 min","36 min","15 sec"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How fast does the earth move in its orbit about the sun?","correct_answer":"18 miles per sec","incorrect_answers":["18 miles per min","18 miles per hour","18 miles per day"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"The moon’s density is what percentage of the earth’s?","correct_answer":"60%","incorrect_answers":["30%","90%","1%"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What region of the Earth experiences the least seasonal variation?","correct_answer":"The equatorial region","incorrect_answers":["North of the equator","South of the equator"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the largest living organism visible from the earth’s orbit?","correct_answer":"The Great Barrier Reef","incorrect_answers":["Mount Everest","The Great Lakes"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What Percentage of Earth’s surface is land?","correct_answer":"About 30%","incorrect_answers":["About 70%","About 10%","About 50%"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which planet other than Earth was the first to be studied by a satellite launched from Earth?","correct_answer":"Venus","incorrect_answers":["Mercury","Mars","Jupiter"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the average distance from Earth to the moon?","correct_answer":"239,000 miles","incorrect_answers":["10 miles","597,000 miles","143,213 miles"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How long does it take for radio signals to travel from Earth to the Moon (and vice versa)?","correct_answer":"1.28 sec","incorrect_answers":["50.43 sec","1 min","20.56 sec"]},{"category":"Earth, Sun, and Moon Trivia","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is the brightest star in the sky (excluding our sun and novas)?","correct_answer":"Sirius","incorrect_answers":["Vega","Canopus"]}]}
